<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

	<string id="csky_nosorog_outfit_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]One of Novikov's "little" projects. Clear Sky veterans had raised concerns about the new exoskeleton models fielded by the more well equiped factions. While there is little worry of hostilities with Duty or Freedom, they were troubled by the thought of Spetsnaz squads or unscrupulous mercs encouraged to assault the Great Swamp behind a Nosorog armor, or worse, Monolith cultists finally breaking past the Barrier.\n
		Calling a favor from friendly merc contacts, the technician got to work into designing an answer to the Nosorogs fielded by other factions. Being last to the race has its own benefits in learning from others's mistakes and successes. But only the most trusted members of the faction are considered for carrying this armor.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBLE WITH: Clear Sky's specialized Nosorog mod kit</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ecolog_nosorog_outfit_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An official version of the military Nosorog, originally intended for Army affiliated stalkers, now being provided to trusted guards of the Scientists. Part of the push by the Government to provide the Scientists with more than just military equipment, this suit is made to help Scientists with their expeditions and explorations into The Zone. Despite hiring Stalkers of dubious legality, due protection is required by everyone facing against the dangers of The Zone.\n
		Despite lacking the ballistic capabilities of other Nosorogs, this suit seeks to provide an adequate amount of protection against all forms of damage while increasing Anomalous and Rupture resistance.\n
		A snafu on distribution caused the first samples of the outfit to arrive in a plain white. The members of Iskra complained about looking like ambulances, and requested a greenish pattern, so that it could be useful in both wildlife observation and combat.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBLE WITH: Specialized Nosorog upgrade mod kit</text>
	</string>

</string_table>